Harriet F. Pilpel Papers, 1913-1981
Sophia Smith Collection, Smith College
- SERIES II. INDIVIDUAL STATES AND TERRITORIES 1913-81
  - New Hampshire
    - Abortion
      - General, 1972-73 (Box 21, Folder 7)
      - Funding, 1976-77 (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - Minors, 1971-72 (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - Reproductive rights, 1972-73 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - New Jersey
    - Abortion
      - General, 1972-79 (Box 21, Folder 11)
      - Facilities and staff, 1972-79 (Box 21, Folder 12)
      - Funding, 1973-79 (Box 21, Folder 13-14)
    - Contraception, 1967, 1972-79, undated (Box 21, Folder 15-16)
    - Family planning, 1970-78 (Box 21, Folder 17)
    - Minors
      - General, 1968-76, undated (Box 21, Folder 18)
      - Contraception, 1975-78 (Box 21, Folder 19)
    - Paternal rights, 1977 (Box 21, Folder 20)
    - Reproductive rights, 1971-78, undated (Box 21, Folder 21)
    - Sterilization
      - Involuntary, 1979 (Box 21, Folder 22)
      - Negligence, 1975 (Box 21, Folder 23)
      - Voluntary, 1975-76 (Box 21, Folder 24)
  - New Mexico
    - Abortion, 1969 (Box 21, Folder 25)
    - Reproductive rights, 1971-80 (Box 21, Folder 26)
    - Sterilization, circa 1973 (Box 21, Folder 27)
  - New York
    - Abortion
      [See also SERIES I. UNITED STATES-Supreme Court-Califano v. McRae]
      - General, 1966-81 (Box 22, Folder 1-3)
      - Anniversary of Roe v. Wade, 1974 (Box 22, Folder 4)
      - Facilities and staff, 1966-80 (Box 22, Folder 5-7)
      - Funding, 1971-80 (Box 22, Folder 8-10)
      - New York City, 1971-77 (Box 22, Folder 11)
      - Politicians' voting records, 1970-80 (Box 22, Folder 12)
      - Registration of fetal deaths, 1972-77 (Box 22, Folder 13)
    - Consent, 1970-78 (Box 22, Folder 14)
      [See also Sterilization]
    - Contraception, 1974-81 (Box 22, Folder 15)
    - Family planning, 1973-79 (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - Legislation and statutes, 1959-77 (Box 23, Folder 2-3)
    - Minors
      [See SERIES I. UNITED STATES-Supreme Court--Carey v. Population Services International]
      - General, 1970-78 (Box 23, Folder 4)
      - Blumenthal Bill, 1970-72 (Box 23, Folder 5)
      - Contraception, 1965-77 (Box 23, Folder 6)
      - New York State Senate Committee on Health, 1971 (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - Reproductive rights
      - General, 1976-81, undated (Box 23, Folder 8)
      - Organizations 1967-79 (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - Sex-oriented advertisements, 1971 (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - Sterilization
      - Carter-Burden Bill, 1977 (Box 23, Folder 11)
      - Involuntary, 1976 (Box 23, Folder 12)
      - Mentally incompetent, 1976-77 (Box 23, Folder 13)
      - Negligence, 1978-79 (Box 23, Folder 14)
      - Voluntary, 1970-77 (Box 23, Folder 15-18)
  - North Carolina
    - Abortion
      - General, 1970-74 (Box 24, Folder 1-4)
      - Funding, 1978 (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - Minors, 1978 (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - Reproductive rights, 1971 (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - Sterilization, 1974-77 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - North Dakota
    - Abortion, 1972-80 (Box 24, Folder 9-12)
    - Minors, 1981 (Box 24, Folder 13)
    - Reproductive rights, 1971, 1979 (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - Ohio
    - Abortion
      - General, 1970-80 (Box 24, Folder 15-17)
      - Facilities and staff, 1976-78 (Box 24, Folder 18)
      - Funding, 1974-80 (Box 24, Folder 19)
    - Consent, 1974-76 (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Contraception, 1967-72 (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - Minors, 1961-76 (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - Sterilization, circa 1971 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Oklahoma
    - Abortion
      - General, 1972-78 (Box 25, Folder 5)
      - Funding, 1977-78 (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - Minors
      - General, 1975-78 (Box 25, Folder 7)
      - Contraception, 1979 (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - Reproductive rights, 1971, 1979-81 (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - Sterilization
      - Involuntary, 1941 (Box 25, Folder 10)
      - Voluntary, 1974-77 (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Oregon
    - Abortion, 1973-78, undated (Box 25, Folder 12)
    - Contraception, 1975-77 (Box 25, Folder 13)
    - Reproductive rights, 1971-75 (Box 25, Folder 14)
    - Sterilization, 1970-71 (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - Pennsylvania
    - Abortion
      [See also SERIES I. UNITED STATES-Supreme Court- Beal v. Franklin; Doe v. Beal ]
      - General, 1971-79 (Box 25, Folder 16-17)
      - Abortion Control Act, 1974-76 (Box 25, Folder 18)
      - Facilities and staff, 1973-79 (Box 25, Folder 19)
      - Funding, 1973-80 (Box 25, Folder 20-21)
    - Consent, 1969, 1974 (Box 25, Folder 22)
    - Contraception advertisements, 1971-78 (Box 25, Folder 23)
    - Family planning, 1973-74 (Box 25, Folder 24)
    - Minors, 1970-75 (Box 25, Folder 25)
    - Reproductive rights
      - General, 1975, 1979, undated (Box 25, Folder 26)
      - Wilkes-Barre Scranton controversy, 1975-76 (Box 25, Folder 27)
    - Sterilization
      - Involuntary, 1974-78 (Box 25, Folder 28)
      - Voluntary, 1978 (Box 25, Folder 29)
  - Puerto Rico, 1971-78 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Rhode Island
    - Abortion
      - General, 1970-77 (Box 26, Folder 2)
      - Facilities and staff, 1974-79 (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - Sterilization, 1975 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - South Carolina
    - Abortion, 1970-77 (Box 26, Folder 5)
      [See also SERIES I--UNITED STATES-Supreme Court-Anders v. Floyd]
    - Family planning, 1973 (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - Minors, 1960-71 (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - Sterilization
      - General, 1959-79 (Box 26, Folder 8)
      - Involuntary, 1968-78 (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - Venereal disease, 1970 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - South Dakota
    - Abortion, 1970-78 (Box 26, Folder 11)
    - Minors, 1977-78 (Box 26, Folder 12)
    - Reproductive rights, 1971 (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - Tennessee
    - Abortion, 1973-81 (Box 26, Folder 14)
    - Contraception, 1976 (Box 26, Folder 15)
    - Minors, 1971-75, undated (Box 26, Folder 16)
    - Reproductive rights, 1974-77, undated (Box 26, Folder 17)
      [See also SERIES I. UNITED STATES-Supreme Court--Nashville Gas Company v. Satty]
    - Sterilization, 1971-78 (Box 26, Folder 18)
  - Texas
    - Abortion
      [See also SERIES I. UNITED STATES-Supreme Court-Roe v. Wade]
      - General, 1974-79 (Box 26, Folder 19)
      - Facilities and staff, 1972-79 (Box 26, Folder 20)
    - Contraception, 1976 (Box 26, Folder 21)
    - Minors, 1974-76 (Box 26, Folder 22)
    - Reproductive rights, 1971-79 (Box 26, Folder 23)
    - Sterilization
      - Mentally incompetent, 1977-81 (Box 26, Folder 24)
      - Voluntary, 1972-75 (Box 26, Folder 25)
  - Utah
    - Abortion
      - General, 1972-78 (Box 26, Folder 26-27)
      - Funding, 1970-80 (Box 26, Folder 28-30)
    - Minors, 1971-77 (Box 26, Folder 31)
      [See also SERIES I. UNITED STATES--Supreme Court- T.H. v. Jones; Doe v. Planned Parenthood Association of Utah; H. L. v. Matheson ]
    - Reproductive rights, 1971-77 (Box 26, Folder 32)
    - Sterilization, 1972 (Box 26, Folder 33)
  - Vermont
    - Abortion, 1971-77 (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - Minors, 1975, undated (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - Reproductive rights, 1971-76 (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - Sterilization, 1975-78 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Virgin Islands, 1971-76, undated (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Virginia
    - Abortion
      [See also SERIES I. UNITED STATES-Supreme Court-Bigelow v. Commonwealth]
      - General,, 1972-78 (Box 27, Folder 6)
      - Funding, 1978-79 (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - Contraception (Box 27)
      [See also SERIES I. UNITED STATES--Supreme Court-Virginia State Board of Pharmacy v. Virginia Citizens Consumer Council]
    - Minors
      - General, 1971-77 (Box 27, Folder 8)
      - Sterilization, 1971-72 (Box 27, Folder 9)
    - Reproductive rights, 1972-75 (Box 27, Folder 10)
    - Sterilization
      - General, 1981, undated (Box 27, Folder 11)
      - Voluntary, 1976 (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Washington
    - Contraception, 1971-73 (Box 27, Folder 13)
    - Minors
      - General, 1969-72, undated (Box 27, Folder 14)
      - Abortion, 1970-72 (Box 27, Folder 15)
    - Reproductive rights, 1971-72 (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - West Virginia
    - Abortion, 1975-79 (Box 27, Folder 17)
    - Reproductive rights, 1969-72 (Box 27, Folder 18)
    - Sterilization, 1974-79 (Box 27, Folder 19)
  - Wisconsin
    - Abortion
      [See also SERIES I. UNITED STATES-Supreme Court--Withrow v. Larkin]
      - Facilities and staff, 1970-77 (Box 27, Folder 20)
      - Funding, 1975-79 (Box 27, Folder 21)
    - Contraception, 1972-76 (Box 27, Folder 22)
    - Minors, 1972-77 (Box 27, Folder 23)
    - Reproductive rights, 1971-72 (Box 27, Folder 24)
    - Sterilization, 1973, 1980 (Box 27, Folder 25)
  - Wyoming
    - Abortion, 1973-78 (Box 27, Folder 26)
    - Reproductive rights, 1971, undated (Box 27, Folder 27)
- SERIES III. INTERNATIONAL 1967-79
  - Abortion, 1967-74 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Family planning and population programs
    - General, 1972-79 (Box 28, Folder 2-4)
    - Population treaty, 1971 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Status of women, 1976, undated (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Sterilization, 1976-78 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Individual countries
    - Cambodia (Box 28)
      [See Indochina]
    - Canada
      - Abortion, 1973-77 (Box 28, Folder 8)
      - Sterilization, 1978-79 (Box 28, Folder 9)
    - China, 1975-78, undated (Box 28, Folder 10)
    - England
      - Abortion, 1967-79, undated (Box 28, Folder 11)
      - Status of women, 1976 (Box 28, Folder 12)
      - Sterilization, 1975, undated (Box 28, Folder 13)
    - France, 1972-76, undated (Box 28, Folder 14)
    - Germany, 1974-76 (Box 28, Folder 15)
    - India, 1978-79 (Box 28, Folder 16)
    - Indochina, 1975 (Box 28, Folder 17)
    - Indonesia, 1979, undated (Box 28, Folder 18)
    - Ireland (Box 28)
      [See England-Status of women]
    - Israel, 1976-77 (Box 28, Folder 19)
    - Italy, 1971-79 (Box 28, Folder 20)
    - Laos (Box 28)
    - Lebanon, ca. 1970 (Box 28, Folder 21)
    - Mexico, 1975 (Box 28, Folder 22)
    - Russia, 1974 (Box 28, Folder 23)
    - Spain, 1974 (Box 28, Folder 24)
    - Thailand, 1979 (Box 28, Folder 25)
    - Vietnam (Box 28)
- OVERSIZE MATERIALS (Drawer 33)
  - Clippings
    - "America's Population Crisis" LOOK, November 21, 1961 (Map-case Flat File)
    - "Birth Control: The Problem We Fear to Face" LOOK, December 5, 1961 (Map-case Flat File)
    - "Inflation Hurts, but Only if Pay Lags--or Stops" New York Times, January 4, 1976 (Map-case Flat File)
  - Newsletter: IPPF (International Planned Parenthood Federation) News, Sept/Oct 1976 (Map-case Flat File)
  - Posters
    - "FPA Made a Difference in 1977-78" (Map-case Flat File)
    - "Wolrd's Children Data Sheet," 1979 (Map-case Flat File)